{
  "openingRemarks": "NB: Enter answers as fractions",
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 180,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(16^{\\frac{1}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(64^{\\frac{2}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "16",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-4)^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{\\dfrac{9}{16}}\\)",
      "answer": "3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(125^{\\frac{2}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "25",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-27)^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "-3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-6)^1\\)",
      "answer": "-6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-216)^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "-6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-6)^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/216",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5^{-2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/25",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-64)^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "-4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-5)^1\\)",
      "answer": "-5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/64",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^1\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-2)^1\\)",
      "answer": "-2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-1)^1\\)",
      "answer": "-1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^{\\frac{3}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/27",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-3)^1\\)",
      "answer": "-3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(27^{\\frac{2}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2^1\\)",
      "answer": "2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(16^{\\frac{3}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "64",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-5)^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/125",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2^{-2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-125)^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "-5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-2)^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{\\dfrac{16}{25}}\\)",
      "answer": "4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(25^{\\frac{1}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3^1\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-1)^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-4)^1\\)",
      "answer": "-4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(25^{\\frac{3}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "125",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8^{\\frac{2}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-6)^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(125^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0^1\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0^0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^{-2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/16",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-3)^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/27",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^{\\frac{1}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(27^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9^{\\frac{3}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "27",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{\\dfrac{4}{9}}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3^{-2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1^1\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-2)^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{\\dfrac{1}{4}}\\)",
      "answer": "1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-8)^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "-2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-4)^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/64",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(64^{\\frac{1}{3}}\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-3)^0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((-5)^{-3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/125",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9^{\\frac{1}{2}}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5^1\\)",
      "answer": "5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix", "cfr"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
